In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to learn how to pronounce the EE as in SHE vowel.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音像SHE中的EE元音。
This vowel is common to many languages.
这个元音在许多语言中都很常见。
To make it, the jaw drops just a little bit.
发这个音时，下巴稍微下垂一点。
The tongue tip stays behind the bottom front teeth.
舌尖保持在下前牙的后面。
The middle front part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth, diminishing the space between the tongue and the roof of the mouth.
舌头的中前部向上拱起，靠近上颚，减少舌头与上颚之间的空间。
The corners of the lips pull a little wide.
嘴角稍微向外拉。
EE.
EE。
They're not quite relaxed.
它们并不完全放松。
Let's see this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个声音。
A little jaw drop, tongue tip down and forward, while the top front of the tongue arches towards the roof of the mouth.
下巴稍微下垂，舌尖向下和向前，而舌头的前上部向上拱起靠近上颚。
The corners of the lips pull out.
嘴角向外拉。
In the word PLEASE, the EE vowel is stressed.
在单词PLEASE中，EE元音是重读的。
Same position.
相同的位置。
When stressed, the vowel has the up-down shape of a stressed syllable.
当重读时，元音具有重读音节的上下形状。
EE.
EE。
When unstressed, it's lower and flatter in pitch, quieter and faster.
当不重读时，音调更低更平，声音更轻更快。
EE.
EE。
This is a very common ending unstressed vowel in American English, because of all of the words that end in Y.
在美式英语中，这是一个非常常见的结尾不重读元音，因为有很多以Y结尾的单词。
Like the word BUSY.
比如单词BUSY。
Let's see this word up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个单词。
Jaw drops, top front of tongue arches up, and the corners of the lips pull out.
下巴下垂，舌头的前上部拱起，嘴角向外拉。
Let's compare the stressed EE in PLEASE, on top, with the unstressed EE in BUSY, on the bottom.
让我们比较一下PLEASE中重读的EE（在上面）和BUSY中不重读的EE（在下面）。
You can see the mouth position for the unstressed EE is a little more relaxed.
你可以看到不重读EE的口型更放松一些。
The jaw doesn't drop as much.
下巴没有那么下垂。
A more relaxed mouth position for the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong is very common, because they are shorter.
元音或双元音的不重读版本通常口型更放松，因为它们更短。
So there's less time to make the full mouth position.
所以没有足够的时间来完成完整的口型。
EE.
EE。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Keep.
EE.
EE。
Keep.
Early.
EE.
EE。
Early.
Police.
EE.
EE。
Police.
Coffee.
EE.
EE。
Coffee.
Meet.
EE.
EE。
Meet.
Each.
EE.
EE。
Each.